We could build a lab.
- 我们可以建立一个实验室
With cool weather forecasting devices!
有着天气预报设备!
-We can invent fantastic machines like the FLDSMDFR. Yeah!
-我们可以创造像超级食物机一样厉害的机器  -没错
-But not that one. -No
-但不是那一个  -不是那个
-Not ever. -Never, ever, ever!
-不是那个  -永远不是
What shall we call our lab?
我们的实验室叫什么名称好呢?
How about Sparkswood?
叫"Sparkswood"怎么样?
Sparkswood.
Sparkswood
-Sparkswood is gonna need some security. -And I can be your mascot!
-Sparkswood需要一位保安  -我可以是你的吉祥物
And I can be your dad.
我可以是你的爸爸
There are many ways in which I can help.
我可以在各种途径提供帮助
Can't forget you, lab partner.
不能忘记你 实验室的合作伙伴
-Steve! -Where'd he get the brown crayon?
-史蒂夫  -他从哪儿拿来的棕色蜡笔
This could be our future.
这可能是我们的未来
Oh, yeah!
哦 是的